host4asp.net 2016-12-02

# Privacy Policy - Host4ASP.NET

Host4ASP.NET regards customers' privacy as the most important matter. We work out this Privacy Policy to show how we collect and use customers' information as well as make a commit for the security and privacy of customers' information. We guarantee that we will never violate this policy.

### Information Collected

Customers are required to provide some personal information when signing up the hosting service. The information includes name, address, email, and phone number, and this type of collected information is used to finish the registration and manage each member's account. Besides, there is also some other information necessary for signing up the service, like credit card and PayPal account. When submitting the order, customers need to offer the credit card number or PayPal account information. 

We use the collected information for multiple purposes, including the service transaction, sales inquiries, support inquiries, and the notification of service. In this case, we have to disclose the information to the banking institutions, affiliates, and contractors. We strictly protect your information from sharing by the third parties, unless under some special conditions. For instance, if customers cooperate with the company to promote a certain service, the company needs to provide a part of customer's personal information, such as the username, name, and address. The information is used for the purpose of enabling customers and the company access to the results of the promotion.

### Domain Registration

Frankly, customer's domain registration information legally has to be published to the public. The information is stored in a database named as WHOIS. Everyone can access to the WHOIS database and view the registration information of each registrant. However, some people may intentionally steal the domain registration information and make use of it to do something illegal. To address this problem, the company uses the alternative information to replace the true information so that customer's domain registration information is not able to be seen by others.

### Social Media

Host4ASP.NET is connected with Google+, Twitter, and Facebook, which include some social media features, like the Like Button of Facebook and the comment section included in each social media. Those features may collect your IP address and track which page you have visited. When making comments to a post, it probably discloses some personal information to public. In this case, customers need to be cautious about their individual information and don't disclose too much privacy when signing up a social media. 

### Customer Surveys

We keep doing customer surveys regularly and encourage our customers to actively join in those surveys. In the survey, customers are required to provide some important information that is used to help us improve the service. In some cases, the survey may be conducted by the third parties. However, we make a solemn promise to remain customer's personal information and responses extremely confidential. Note that customers have the right to determine whether participate in the survey or not. Participation in the customer survey is completely voluntary.

We aggregate the information that we have received from the responding to our customer surveys to create broader responses to the survey questions. For example, the information is about age, gender, hobbies, education, residence, job, or the geographic information. Based on the collected information, we will improve our services and do the best to meet customers' expectations. Thus, customers are able to enjoy more efficient, reliable and trust-worthy services. Meanwhile, the aggregated information does us a favor to develop new products and services. Note that, the aggregated information and the non-personal information may be shared with third parties.

### Data Security

We try our best to keep security of customers' information with the help of industry standard security measure to protect the exchange and transmission of the sensitive data. For some particularly sensitive information, like the credit card number, we encrypt it before transmitting it to our server. And also, we make every effort to ensure the security and integrity of the network and any facilities. In this case, we can guarantee to prevent the private information from stealing and damaging for the breakdown of network. For any information under our control, we make a commitment to take a series security measures to protect the information.

### Legal Disclaimer

Although we are responsible for maintaining the integrity of customer's privacy, we must offer the personal information to the court order or the applicable legal process in the event of illegal behaviors. We declare that we are not responsible for the information loss and damage caused by some special reasons beyond our control, like natural disaster, military conflict, and illegal behaviors. And if customers misoperate the website and have not produced a backup for the data, we assume no responsibility for the data loss or information loss.

### Children's Privacy

Our website is appropriate for people of all ages, but we are not directly towards children under 13 and don't collect any personal information from children themselves. If we are aware that there is personal information collected from a child under 13, we will take measures to delete the information. We suggest that children who are able to send individual information to the company or some other services online to do it after acquiring a permission from their parents.

### Your Responsibility

You need to attach great importance to your individual information like the username and password and don't disclose them to others. In addition, when accessing to some public forums, you need to be cautious about your private information and prevent it from leaking. To keep security of your login information, we suggest you to modify your password regularly and set the password as complicated as possible. Host4ASP.NET allows you to modify, update, and access to your personal information through the control panel, any subject to certain exceptions need to be prescribed by law. You can also modify, update, and access to your personal information by contacting our support staffs via phone, email, and live chat. Please keep updating your contact information and make sure that you are able to receive the information.

### Privacy Policy Revision

Host4ASP.NET reserves the right to revise, amend, or modify this Privacy Policy in any circumstances and at any time. For any revision, amendment, or modification of this Privacy Policy, we will provide you with prior notification in time. We suggest you to keep reviewing this page more often than not.

### Contact Us for Any Questions

If you have any problems about this Privacy Policy, please email support@host4asp.net and let us relieve your confusion.
